Guide to the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers MSS.157
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XI: Media Access Copies, 161949
  - Subseries C: Sound recording Access Copies, 161952
    - Writing File: "George Kuchar", undated; 159658 (Case 157.0148)
    - Writing File: "Tori Interview" YM Magazine, February 27, 2002; 159657 (Case 157.0150)
    - Writing File: "Allison Anders, Things Behind the Sun #1", undated; 159656 (Case 157.0152)
    - Writing File: "Allison Anders, Things Behind the Sun #2", 1992-1994; 159655 (Case 157.0154)
    - Writing File: Run Lola Run, undated; 159654 (Case 157.0156)
    - Writing File: "Penelope Spheeris Sept. 1998", 159653 (Case 157.0158)
      Duration: A) 45 minutes B) unknown
    - Writing File: "Christina Kelly, Sassy Pt 1", undated; 159652 (Case 157.0160)
    - Writing File: "Christina Kelly, Sassy Pt 2, undated; 159651 (Case 157.0162)
    - Writing File: "A) Mary X-mess Spin, Pt 2 B) Steve Duncombe", December 4, 2001; unknown; 159650 (Case 157.0164)
      Duration: A) 20 minutes B) 25 minutes
    - Writing File: "Mark Mothersbaugh!!", 1992-1994; 159649 (Case 157.0166)
    - Writing File: "Tamra YM Interview", undated; 159648 (Case 157.0168)
    - Writing File: "A) Don Letts B) Katja von Gernier Pt 1", undated; 159647 (Case 157.0170)
      Duration: A) 20 minutes B) 30 minutes
    - Writing File: "Katja Von Gernier Pt 2", undated; 159646 (Case 157.0172)
    - Writing File: "A) Cool Teen Favita B) Nikki Reed ", June 26, 2002; June 29, 2002; 159645 (Case 157.0174)
    - Writing File: "Rosewood Follow Up Questions 2/28 and 3/1" YM Article, February 28- March 1,2002; 159644 (Case 157.0176)
    - "Babes: Lori Barbero," Babes in Toyland, February 1997; 159611 (Case 157.0178)
    - "Lori and Dale," Babes in Toyland, undated; 159610 (Case 157.0180)
    - "Dale and Lori," Babes in Toyland, undated; 159609 (Case 157.0182)
      Duration: A) 45 minutes B) 30 minutes.
    - "Babes: Lori," Babes in Toyland, undated; 159608 (Case 157.0184)
    - "Babes: Dana, Kat," Babes in Toyland, undated; 159607 (Case 157.0186)
    - "Babes: Dana," Babes in Toyland, undated; 159606 (Case 157.0188)
    - "Steve Albini", August 24, 1998; 159605 (Case 157.0190)
    - "A) Radical Cheerleaders #1 B) Aimee and Cara", undated; 159604 (Case 157.0192)
    - "Allison Anders", June 1999; 159603 (Case 157.0194)
      Original format: Audiocassette, Access Copy
    - "Becky Johnson Tape 1", undated; 159602 (Case 157.0196)
    - "Becky Johnson Tape 2", 1992; 159601 (Case 157.0198)
    - "Carine Alder Interview", undated; 159600 (Case 157.0200)
    - "Carla Rockergrrl #1", undated; 159599 (Case 157.0202)
    - "Carla Rockergrrl #2", undated; 159598 (Case 157.0204)
    - "Debbie Gordon Tape 1", undated; 159597 (Case 157.0206)
    - "Debbie Gordon Tape 2", undated; 159596 (Case 157.0208)
    - "Jenny L", undated; 159595 (Case 157.0210)
    - "Joe O' Neill Tape 1", undated; 159594 (Case 157.0212)
    - "Joe O' Neill Tape 2", undated; 159593 (Case 157.0214)
    - "A) Silkworm, Tim B) Silkworm, Tim, Andy", undated; 159592 (Case 157.0216)
    - "A) Bis B) Todd Verow", 1992; 159591 (Case 157.0218)
    - "Tamra's Interview", undated; 159590 (Case 157.0220)
- Oversize Series I.B: I Was A Teenage Serial Killer - Production Materials, 159330
  Scope and Content Note
  Contains material related to the production of I Was A Teenage Serial Killer.
  - Promotional Material, 159331
    - Serial Killer: T-shirt, 1993; 159332 (Box 7, Folder 22A)
- Oversize Series II.A: Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore - Production Materials, 159327
  Contains material related to the production of Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore.
  - Production Material, 159328
    - Mary-Jane: Stage Prop, Talking Pee Wee Herman Doll, 1987; 159329 (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_e99ea2df907a80b9420124c07b624d4a)
- Oversize Series II.B: Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore - Distribution and Public Relations, 159324
  Contains material related to promotion of Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore.
  - Promotional Material, 159325
    - Mary Jane: T-shirt, 1996; 159326 (Box 7, Folder 90A)
- Oversize Series IV.D: Professional Projects - Hardcorn, 159321
  Contains material related to Hardcorn Comics.
  - Promotional Material, 159322
    - Hardcorn: T-shirt, 1992; 159323 (Box 7, Folder 186)
- Oversize Series IX: Nostalgia, Neat Things, 159308
  Contains oversize material related to Series IX, "Nostalgia, Neat Things. Items include newspaper clippings, artifacts and photo albums. Arranged chronologically and by format.
  - Photo Album and Scrapbook, 1974-1978; 159320 (Box 9, Folder 393)
  - Photo Album and Scrapbook, 1986-1989; 159319 (Box 9, Folder 394)
  - Photo Album and Scrapbook, 1989-1997; 159318 (Box 9, Folder 395)
  - New York Times, November 26, 1963, 159317 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - San Francisco Examiner, April 20, 1992, 159316 (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, May 1, 1992, 159315 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - San Francisco Examiner, June 3, 1992, 159314 (Box 10, Folder 399)
  - San Francisco Examiner, November 4, 1992, 159313 (Box 10, Folder 400)
  - "1993/1994, Early Writings" clippings, 159312 (Box 10, Folder 401)
  - Nightmare Before Christmas, bag, Undated; 159311 (Box 10, Folder 402)
  - Arlo Guthrie Poster, Undated; 159310 (Box 10, Folder 403)
  - Nightmare Before Christmas Kaleidoscope, Undated; 159309 (Box 11)
- Oversize Series X: Miscellaneous, 159305
  Oversize miscellaneous items.
  - Wall Calendar, 1995; 159307 (Box 10)
- Accretion 2008 - Series I: I Was A Teenage Serial Killer, 1993-2000; 159291
  - Subseries A: Production Materials, 1992; 159303
    - Photo Stills, Contact Sheet, Photo Negatives, 1992; 159304 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Press and Distribution, 1993-1996; 159297
    - Press Pack Materials, 1993-1996; 159302 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Distribution Correspondence, K Records, 1998; 159301 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Video Sleeves, 1999; 159300 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Distribution Invoices, InSound, 2001-2004; 159299 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Distribution Correspondence, Skura Intercontinental Trading Co., 2000; 159298 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: Media Originals, 159292
    Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.
    - "I Was A Teenage Serial Killer", Undated; 159296 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0371, Case 157.0371)
      Format: Mini DV, Donated Element
    - "I Was A Teenage Serial Killer MPR Radio Interview, Sarah Jacobson 8-6-93", 1993; 159295 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0489)
    - "I Was A Teenage Serial Killer", Undated; 159294 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0490)
    - "Sarah + Beth Friend MPR Radio Interview 'I Was Teenage' 8/7/93", 1993; 159293 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0496)
- Accretion 2008 - Series II: Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore, 1994-2006; 159187
  - Subseries A: Production Materials, 1994-2006; 159266
    - Investor Agreements, 1996; 159290 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Crew Deal Memorandum, Heidi M. Smith, 1994-1995; 159289 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Mary Jane Script, Undated; 159288 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "Mary Jane's Not A Script Anymore" - Shooting Script, 1996; 159287 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Photo Contract, Viviane Oh, 1995; 159286 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets + Negatives, 1995; 159285 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Slides, 1995; 159284 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Dream Wedding Photo Negatives, circa 1995; 159283 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - On-Set Photos, 1995; 159282 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - M.J. Prop List, 1996; 159281 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - The Saul Zaentz Company Film Center Agreement, 1996; 159280 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Sound Budgets, 1996; 159279 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Sound Invoice, Poolside Studios, 1996; 159278 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Music Supervisor Agreements and Correspondence, 1996-1999; 159277 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Soundtrack Materials, Azalia Snail, 1996; 159276 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Soundtrack Materials, Babes in Toyland, 1996-1999; 159275 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Soundtrack Materials, The Loudmouths, 1996; 159274 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Soundtrack Materials, New Wet Kojak, 1996; 159273 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Soundtrack Materials, Steel Pole Bath Tub, 1996; 159272 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Trailer Script, 1996; 159271 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - MJ Opticals, 1996; 159270 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - "Scenes For Each Movie" Plan, 1996; 159269 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Print Invoices, Fotokem, 1998-1999; 159268 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Timing Notes, 4MC Labs, 1996; 159267 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Subseries B: Distribution and Public Relations, 1996-2006; 159253
    - "Sarah Jacobson on the Set of Mary Jane" by Lee Jacobson, Photo and Negative, 1996; 159265 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Photo Negatives, 1996; 159264 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Press Pack Materials, Selected Press and Interviews, 1997-1999; 159263 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Press Zine Materials, 1997; 159262 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Artist Information, Chank, 1997; 159261 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Screening Poster Materials and "Virgin" Stickers, 1996-1999; 159260 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Website Correspondence, 2001; 159259 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Video Covers, 1997; 159258 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Distribution Summary, 1997-1999; 159257 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Invoices and Correspondence, Canyon Cinema, 2002-2006; 159256 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, Dieter Kosslick, 1996; 159255 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, Margaret Herrick Library, 1999; 159254 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Subseries C: Media Originals, 159237
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Dub, Audio: 1 & 2 Mono, 1995; 159252 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0354)
      Format: BetaCam SP, Donated Element
      TRT: 00:06:15
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Dub, Part One, 1996; 159251 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0355)
      TRT: 00:52:00
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Dub, Part Two, 1996; 159250 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0356)
      TRT: 00:46:00
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Telecine Print Xfer, Tape #1, 1996; 159249 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0357)
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore Telecine Print Xfer, Tape #2, 1996; 159248 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0358)
    - Mary Jane Is Not a Virgin Anymore Film-to-Tape Transfer @ 24 fps, 1996; 159247 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0359)
      Format: Digital BetaCam, Donated Element
      TRT: 01:38:00
    - "Mary Jane Music", Undated; 159246 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0360)
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Mono Copy R1 + R2, Undated; 159245 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0373)
    - Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Mono Copy R3 + R4, Undated; 159244 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0374)
    - "MJ 2", Undated; 159243 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0375)
    - "MJ 3", Undated; 159242 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0376)
    - Mary Jane "Multi-Track Audio," Foley R - 1 + 2, Undated; 159241 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0377)
    - Mary Jane "Multi-Track Audio," Foley R - 3 + 4, Undated; 159240 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0378)
    - "Mary Jane Movie Audio", Undated; 159239 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0488)
    - "Artifacts on KFAI-FM, Hosted by Marya Morstad, Interview: 'Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore' - Sarah Jacobson, 2-14-97", 1997; 159238 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0497)
  - Subseries F: Objects, Props - Smiley Face Collection, 159188
    - Large Smiley Face Plush with "Smile" Ribbon, Undated; 159236 (Box 25, Object ID: 157.2.0001)
    - Large Plastic Smiley Face, Undated; 159235 (Box 25, Object ID: 157.2.0002)
    - Large Smiley Face Tin Wastebasket, Undated; 159234 (Box 25, Object ID: 157.2.0003)
    - Ben Geffen Smiley Face Address Labels, Undated; 159233 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0004)
      Biographical/Historical Note
      Ben Geffen is Sarah Jacobson's friend from New York, who now lives in Seattle, WA. He collected most of the Smiley Face Collection.
    - Ben Geffen Smiley Face Address Label Collage, Undated; 159232 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0005)
    - Mr. Happy by Roger Hargreaves, 1980; 159231 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0006)
    - Mr. Happy Small Plush Pouch, Undated; 159230 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0007)
    - Trio of Smiley Face Plastic Balloons, Undated; 159229 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0008)
    - Smiley Face Ribbon, Undated; 159228 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0009)
    - Smiley Face Lunch Mates Bag, Undated; 159227 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0010)
    - Smiley Face Rectangular Patch, Undated; 159226 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0011)
    - Freedom Foursquare Church Prayer Card, Undated; 159225 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0012)
    - "Smile Jesus Loves You" Miniature Pamphlet, Undated; 159224 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0013)
    - "Try God" Miniature Pamphlet, Undated; 159223 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0014)
    - MAD Magazine, No. 150, April 1972, 159222 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0015)
    - Assorted Smiley Face Buttons and Pendants, Undated; 159221 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0016)
    - Smiley Face Rain Poncho, Undated; 159220 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0017)
    - Smiley Face Hand Mirror, Undated; 159219 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0018)
    - Smiley Face Fancy Nails Set, Undated; 159218 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0019)
    - "Have A Nice Day" Wire Hanger, Undated; 159217 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0020)
    - Pair of Bendy Figurines, Undated; 159216 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.0021)
    - Bright Pink Smiley Face Plush Keyring, Undated; 159215 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0022)
    - Red Smiley Face Eyewear Case, Undated; 159214 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0023)
    - Blue Smiley Face Eyewear Case, Undated; 159213 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0024)
    - Trio of Smiley Face Rubber Stamps, Undated; 159212 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0025)
    - Wind-Up Smiley Face Toy, Undated; 159211 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0026)
    - Smiley Face Night Light, Undated; 159210 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0027)
    - Smiley Face Golf Ball, Undated; 159209 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0028)
    - Smiley Face Rock, Undated; 159208 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0029)
    - Smiley Face Inflatable, Undated; 159207 (Box 26, Object ID: 157.2.0030)
    - Trio of "Have A Happy Day" Plastic Yellow Cups, Undated; 159206 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0031)
    - Single "Have A Happy Day" Plastic Yellow Mug, Undated; 159205 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0032)
    - Blue and White Smiley Face Mug, Undated; 159204 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0033)
    - Black and Yellow Smiley Face Mug, Undated; 159203 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0034)
    - Orange and Black Smiley Face Mug, Undated; 159202 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0035)
    - Yellow Smiley Face Ceramic Mug, Undated; 159201 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0036)
    - White and Green Smiley Face Glass Mug, Undated; 159200 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0037)
    - Smiley Face Glass Goblet, Undated; 159199 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0038)
    - Smiley Face Plastic Flower Knick-Knack, Undated; 159198 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0039)
    - Smiley Face Salt & Pepper Set, 1995; 159197 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0040)
    - Pair of Smiley Face Plastic Yellow Plates, Undated; 159196 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0041)
    - "Have A Happy Day" Plastic Yellow Miniature Tray, Undated; 159195 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0042)
    - "Have A Happy Day" Red and Yellow Smiley Face Alarm Clock, Undated; 159194 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0043)
    - "Have A Happy Day" White and Yellow Wall Clock, Undated; 159193 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0044)
    - Large Yellow Smiley Face Foot Scale, Undated; 159192 (Box 27, Object ID: 157.2.0045)
    - Large Smiley Face Tin Tray, Undated; 159191 (Object ID: 157.2.0046)
    - Large Smiley Face Tin Tray with "Have a Nice Day", Undated; 159190 (Object ID: 157.2.0047)
    - Bread Box Bakery Discount Store, "Have a Happy Day!!" Smiley Face Book Dusk Jacket, 1975; 159189 (Box 24, Object ID: 157.2.0048)
- Accretion 2008 - Series III: The Stains Documentary, 1980-1999; 159175
  - Subseries A: Production Materials, 1980-1999; 159183
    - Interviews and Correspondence, Nancy Dowd, 1997-1999; 159186 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Notes and Contact Information, 1998-1999; 159185 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - "Ladies and Gentlemen..." Photo Stills, 1980; 159184 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Subseries B: Media Originals, 159176
    Conditions Governings Access
    - "Ladies + Gentlemen, The Fabulous Stains, Tape #1", Undated; 159182 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0361)
    - "Ladies + Gentlemen, The Fabulous Stains, Tape #2", Undated; 159181 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0362)
    - "Misc. Film Clips - Stains ", Undated; 159180 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0363)
    - "Behind the Movie: The Fabulous Stains", Undated; 159179 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0379)
    - "Stains - CUFF", 1997-1998; 159178 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.038, Box 11)
      Format: Hi 8 Video, Donated Element
    - "Stains Interviews - Beat Kitchen", Undated; 159177 (Box 28, Media ID: 157.0381)
- Accretion 2008 - Series IV: Professional Projects, 158958
  - Subseries A: Station Wagon Productions, 1993-2006; 159148
    - Catalog, Undated; 159174 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Distribution Notebook, 1995-1998; 159173 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Budgets, 1997-1998; 159172 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Grants, 1993-1999; 159171 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Fundraising, 2001; 159170 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Check Stubs, 1995-1998; 159169 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Better Property Managment Lease, 1996; 159168 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Production Invoices, 1997-1998; 159167 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Wells Fargo Statements, 1997-1999; 159166 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Tax Returns, 1991-1994; 159165 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Tax Returns, Budget Duplicates, 1993-1996; 159164 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Income Tax Returns, 1995-1998; 159163 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - "Finance - Tax Things", 1998-1999; 159162 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - "My Film Stuff" - Screening and Festival Materials, 1993-2003; 159161 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - "New Website" Note, Undated; 159160 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Crossroads Films Press Release, Undated; 159159 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Photos of Sarah and Ruth by Julie Pavlowski, 1996; 159158 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Station Wagon Productions Business Cards, Undated; 159157 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Contacts, Business Cards, Undated; 159156 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Mailing Lists, Undated; 159155 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence 1, 1993-1996; 159154 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Correspondence 2, 1997-1998; 159153 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Correspondence 3, 1999-2005; 159152 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1996-1999; 159151 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Unmailed Correspondence by Sarah, Undated; 159150 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Film II Ledger Notebook, Undated; 159149 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Subseries B: Sleaze, 1995-2003; 159127
    - Babes in Toyland Press, 1995; 159147 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - "Chicks in Rock" Collected Press Clips, 1980-2002; 159146 (Box 19, Folder 73A)
    - Sleaze Scrapbook Materials 1 of 2, 2000-2001; 159145 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Sleaze Scrapbook Materials 2 of 2, 2000-2001; 159144 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Sleaze Scrapbook, 2001-2002; 159143 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Sleaze Plot Synopsis and Summary, Undated; 159142 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Sleaze Script, Undated; 159141 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - "Sleaze Script With Jim's Notes", Undated; 159140 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - "Questions for Possible Producers" and To-Do List for Andrea Sperlinge, Undated; 159139 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - "Power Revision" by Robert E. Byrd, Scr(i)pt Mag, 2003; 159138 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Sleaze Rockefeller Proposal, 2000; 159137 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Sleaze "Sneak Peak" Event, Sneak Preview Entertainment and Fifth Night, 2000; 159136 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Notebook, 2001-2002; 159135 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Notebook, Undated; 159134 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - Production Agreement and Script Notes, Mark J. Huisman, 2001; 159133 (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - "Sleaze Notes", Undated; 159132 (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - "Matt's Sleaze Notes", 2003; 159131 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    - Soundtrack List, Undated; 159130 (Box 19, Folder 89)
    - "Sleaze Receipts", 2002; 159129 (Box 19, Folder 90)
    - Sleaze Copyright Information, 2002; 159128 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Subseries C: The Adventures of Sweet Miss: The Disco Years, 1988; 159125
    - Sweet Miss Production Materials, 1988; 159126 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Subseries E: Film Festivals and Concerts, 1999; 159123
    - 6th Annual Chicago Underground Film Festival Program, 1999; 159124 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Subseries F: VH1, 2001-2003; 159120
    - Radical Cheerleaders Materials and Research, 2001; 159122 (Box 19, Folder 94)
    - Correspondence, 2003; 159121 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Subseries G: Oxygen Media, 1999-2000; 159115
    - Offer of Employment, 1999; 159119 (Box 19, Folder 96)
    - Correspondence, Woodstock "Rapestock/Hellstock", 1999; 159118 (Box 19, Folder 97)
    - Correspondence, Sneak Preview, 1999; 159117 (Box 19, Folder 98)
    - Recommendation for Lauren Monocell, 2000; 159116 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Subseries H: 50/50, 2000-2005; 159112
    - STIGMA Manifesto, 2002-2003; 159114 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    - Alice Locas Materials, 2000-2005; 159113 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Subseries I: Writing Files, 1988-2003; 159054
    - "Sarah's Novel," Book 1 of 2, 1990; 159111 (Box 20, Folder 102)
    - "Sarah's Novel," Book 2 of 2, 1990; 159110 (Box 20, Folder 103)
    - Resumes and Biography, 1990-2003; 159109 (Box 20, Folder 104)
    - Cover Letters, 2000-2003; 159108 (Box 20, Folder 105)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Unedited Interviews, 1997; 159107 (Box 20, Folder 106)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Edited Interviews, 1997; 159106 (Box 20, Folder 107)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Introduction, 1997; 159105 (Box 20, Folder 108)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Draft, 1997; 159104 (Box 20, Folder 109)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Published Version, 1997; 159103 (Box 20, Folder 110)
    - The Stains Article for Grand Royal Magazine, Correspondence, 1996-1997; 159102 (Box 20, Folder 111)
    - "Dry", 1993; 159101 (Box 20, Folder 112)
    - "Sex At the Movies" A Screenplay by Sarah Jacobson, 1993; 159100 (Box 20, Folder 113)
    - Freelance Writing, Published Articles, 1996-2001; 159099 (Box 20, Folder 114)
    - "Old Projects, Outlines", 1999-2002; 159098 (Box 20, Folder 115)
    - Playboy, Freelance Drafts, 2001; 159097 (Box 20, Folder 116)
    - Pitches and Proposals, 2001-2003; 159096 (Box 20, Folder 117)
    - IFC Teen Film Pitch, 2001; 159095 (Box 20, Folder 118)
    - Script Proposals, 2000-2002; 159094 (Box 20, Folder 119)
    - Freelance Drafts, 2000-2001; 159093 (Box 20, Folder 120)
    - "Old Projects: Blackout Books Log", 2000; 159092 (Box 20, Folder 121)
    - YM Magazine Rosewood Prison Research, 2002; 159091 (Box 20, Folder 122)
    - YM Magazine Rosewood Prison Consent Forms, 2002; 159090 (Box 20, Folder 123)
    - YM Magazine Rosewood Prison Article Notebook, 2002; 159089 (Box 20, Folder 124)
    - "High School Reunion" Production Materials, 1988-2002; 159088; This file includes objects related to Sarah Jacobson's Edina High School experience, including a letterman patch and photographs. (Box 20, Folder 125)
    - "High School Reunion" Synopsis and Biography, 2002-2003; 159087 (Box 20, Folder 126)
    - Much Music, "Adam Tastemaker" Schedule, 2002; 159086 (Box 20, Folder 127)
    - "Popular Is Hell" Research, 2002; 159085 (Box 20, Folder 128)
    - "Rock 'n Roll Parking Lot" Production Bid Paperwork, 2002; 159084 (Box 20, Folder 129)
    - "Backtracks" TV Proposal and Production Materials, 2003; 159083 (Box 20, Folder 130)
    - Freelance Writing, Correspondence, 2001-2005; 159082 (Box 20, Folder 131)
    - "Goals for 2002", 159081 (Box 20, Folder 132)
    - "Celebrity High School Reunion" Pitch, Undated; 159080 (Box 20, Folder 133)
    - "Puppetistas" Notes, Undated; 159079 (Box 20, Media 134)
    - U MTV Notes, Undated; 159078 (Box 20, Folder 135)
    - "Freakathon" Scrapbook Materials 1 of 2, Undated; 159077 (Box 20, Folder 136)